meetcam.com 2006-10-23

# MeetCam.com Adult Webcam Chat Community with Voice Chat Rooms.

#### Privacy Policy

This privacy statement explains data collection and use practices of the [http://MeetCam.com](http://meetcam.com/) site (the "Site") owned by MeetCam.   
By accessing the Site, you are consenting to the information collection and use practices described in this privacy statement.

Collecting Your Personal Information: We will collect personal information if you choose to register on the Site. The personal information we collect includes your email address, address and other personal information which you filled in Registration page. 

You are requested to create a user name to participate in MeetCam, which is the name you will be known by to others in this public community. Please keep in mind that if you disclose personal information in the Forums, this information may be collected and used by others. MeetCam cautions you against giving out personal information to strangers online, which they may use for illegal or harmful purposes. 

The Site may collect certain anonymous information about your visit, such as the name of the Internet service provider and the Internet Protocol (IP) address through which you access the Internet; the date and time you access the Site; the pages that you access while at the Site and the Internet address of the Web site from which you linked directly to our site. None of this information is personally-identifiable. This anonymous information is used to help improve the Site, analyze trends, and administer the Site. 

Use of your Personal Information: The personal information MeetCam collects will be used to provide the service(s) or carry out the transaction(s) you have requested or authorized. This may include using the personal information to

-To understand feature requirements for our services.   
-To send updates about our services.

MeetCam may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served to MeetCam, or the Site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of MeetCam and our family of Web sites; or (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of MeetCam employees, users of MeetCam products or services, or members of the public. 

Personal information collected on the Site may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which MeetCam or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities, and by using this site, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country. 

Control of your Personal Information: Except as otherwise described in this statement, personal information you provide on the Site will not be shared outside of MeetCam and its controlled subsidiaries and affiliates without your permission. It will only be used for the purposes stated above. 

Please be aware that this privacy statement and the choices you make on the Site will not necessarily apply to personal information you may have provided to MeetCam in the context of other, separately operated, MeetCam products or services. 

Access to your Personal Information: Customer information collected by MeetCam stored at our database, plus sent back to MeetCam. You can review and edit information stored at MeetCam by login to your account. 

Security of your Personal Information: MeetCam is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. For example, we store the personal information you provide on computer servers with limited access that are located in controlled facilities. Additionally, when we transmit sensitive personal information (such as a credit card number) over the Internet, we protect it through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol. 

Cookies: We use cookies on this Site to ensure the integrity of the registration process. We use a session cookie, meaning it expires soon after you leave the registration process, and is not placed on your hard drive unless you specify you wish to "log on automatically." 

Use of Web Beacons: Pages on the Site may contain electronic images known as Web beacons - sometimes called single-pixel gifs - that allow the Site to count users who have visited those pages. We may include web beacons in promotional e-mail messages in order to count how many messages have been opened and acted upon. Web beacons are not used to access your personal information; they are a technique we use to compile aggregated statistics about Site usage. 

Web beacons collect only a limited set of information including a cookie number, time and date of a page view, and a description of the page on which the Web beacon resides. 

Links to Other Web Sites: This Site may contain links to other Web sites. Please be aware that this Privacy Policy applies solely to the information collected on the Site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other Web sites. We encourage you to be aware when you are leaving this Site and read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that you visit before providing any personally identifiable information. 

Changes to This Privacy Statement: We may occasionally update this privacy statement. When we do, we will also revise the "last updated" date at the top of the privacy statement. For material changes to this privacy statement, we will notify you either by placing a prominent notice on the home page of our web site or by directly sending you a notification. We encourage you to periodically review this privacy statement to stay informed about how we are protecting the personal information we collect. Your continued use of the service constitutes your agreement to this privacy statement and any updates. 

Contact Information: MeetCam welcomes your comments regarding this privacy statement. If you believe that MeetCam has not adhered to this privacy statement, please contact us by e-mail at [support@MeetCam.com](mailto:support@MeetCam.com) or via postal mail at the address provided below, and we will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
